DARLA **Brown**

SUMMARY

Demonstrated the ability to complete tasks accurately, despite interruptions and competing demands. Creative professional with extensive project, experience from concept to development. I am an innovator, that always figuring a way to create new content.

SKILLS

Technical Skills **Personal Skills**

React.is - React-native JavaScript - HTML I have written 3 novels, and working on my Bootstrap-python

/ CSS - - Bash - Git -Redux-typescript - API- 4th. I have also written 3 features and one TV pilot film scripts and currently working my 5th screenplay. And written 11 songs for a soundtrack

EXPERIENCE

10/2002 to 02/2019 Medical Secretary, and Billing Technician

Alameda Health System – Oakland, CA

- Digitized over data transition medical records and organized files into company's system using Solarian
- Company' clinics office activities, including customer service, patient appointment management, billing and collections, and office administration
- Supervised and trained admitting, billing and collection staff
- Managed medical supply inventory, insurance records, patient charts and company files using online tracking system

09/2021 to Present

2021

2021 2019 React-Native and React apprentice

Alpha-works Apprenticeship—Oakland, CA

Scrum, Agile projects in React and React-Native, Github and Git Flow/project board working and QA on real client project, team building exercise, co-teaching.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2019 Kickstart Coding bootcamp – Oakland, CA

> Coursework included final projects in Python, JavaScript, and Computer Science fundamentals Wed development Full stack

2019 to 2020 Women Who Code San Francisco/Oakland _co-lead assisting lead with planning and

organizing meeting and meetup. Soliciting sponsors for mentorship. Planning study

group for preparing algorithm white board test. Study group mentors support.

2021 Bitwise Industries bootcamp –Oakland, CA

Coursework include Javascript, React, Redux, Github using VS code